A Guide to the Records of the Secretary of the Commonwealth, 1996-2006
Library of Virginia
- Series VII. Extradition Requisitions and Renditions, 2002-2005 (accessions 42418 and 42513)., Extent: 16.8 cu. ft. (Box 88-136)
  - Subseries B: Extradition Renditions
    - 2004 (Accession 42418)
      - Stallings - Walton (Box 132, Folder 2)
      - Weaver - Williams (Box 132, Folder 3)
      - Yancy - Yong (Box 132, Folder 4)
    - 2005 (Accession 42513)
      - Abrams - Bates (Box 133, Folder 1)
      - Bowman - Coleman (Box 133, Folder 2)
      - Coleman - Curtis (Box 133, Folder 3)
      - Darrin - Fenner (Box 133, Folder 4)
      - Fitzgerald - Frazier (Box 133, Folder 5)
      - Garner - Harris (Box 134, Folder 1)
      - Hartless - Horne (Box 134, Folder 2)
      - Howard - Johnson (Box 134, Folder 3)
      - Johnson - Leonard (Box 134, Folder 4)
      - Little - Mejia (Box 134, Folder 5)
      - Moore - Muse (Box 135, Folder 1)
      - Owens - Powell (Box 135, Folder 2)
      - Powers - Reid (Box 135, Folder 3)
      - Roberts - Sherman (Box 135, Folder 4)
      - Stephenson - Styron (Box 135, Folder 5)
      - Surratt - Thurman (Box 136, Folder 1)
      - Tompkins - White (Box 136, Folder 2)
      - White - Yang (Box 136, Folder 3)
- Series VIII. Notary Public Register, 2002-2005 (accessions 42418)., Extent: 0.35 cu. ft. (Box 137)
  This series consists of an annual printout that documents the registration of persons appointed to be notaries public by the Secretary of the Commonwealth between 2002 and 2005 and the date they were appointed.
  - Notary Public Register (part one) (Box 137, Folder 1)
  - Notary Public Register (part two) (Box 137, Folder 2)
  - Notary Public Register (part three) (Box 137, Folder 3)
- Series IX. Restoration of Rights Files, 1996-2006 (accessions 42418 and 42513) RESTRICTED FOR 75 YEARS., Extent: 47.60 cu. ft. (Box 138-274)
  Series documents the restoration of rights that were granted by Governor Mark R. Warner (2002-2006). Also included are files for a few restoration of rights granted by Governors George F. Allen (1996) and James S. Gilmore (1998-2002) that were not previously transferred to the Library of Virginia. The files are arranged into two subseries: Allen and Gilmore, 1996-2002 and Warner, 2002-2006. Each file includes a copy of the restoration of rights certificate, original application, recommendation letters, parole information, and police record checks. The files are arranged by year and alphabetically by name therein. This series contains confidential and privacy-protected information. Access is restricted for 75 years after date of creation per Code of Virginia 42.1-78.
  - Subseries A: Allen and Gilmore, 1996-2002 (accession 42418).
    - Garner, Raymond Wayne, granted 18 September 1996 (Box 138, Folder 1)
    - Crommelin, Quentin, Jr., granted 10 January 2002 (Box 138, Folder 2)
    - Gray, William Leslie, granted 22 October 2001 (Box 138, Folder 3)
    - Houchins, Roger D., granted 11 January 2002 (Box 138, Folder 3a)
    - Lewett, Linda Mary, granted ca. February 2002(?) (Box 138, Folder 4)
    - Lovern, David Conley, granted ca. October 2000 (?) (Box 138, Folder 5)
  - Subseries B: Governor Mark R. Warner, 2002-2006.
    - 12 January 2002 to 22 January 2003 (Accession 42418)
      - Adcock, Joseph Franklin, granted 15 December 2002 (Box 138, Folder 6)
      - Addison, Roger Patrick, granted 2 August 2002 (Box 138, Folder 7)
      - Alldredge, Michael Wayne, granted 15 December 2002 (Box 138, Folder 8)
      - Allen, Wilbert Charles, Jr., granted 5 September 2002 (Box 138, Folder 8a)
      - Armbrister, Lenwood Dale, granted 10 October 2002 (Box 138, Folder 9)
      - Arthur, Gene Edward, granted 9 October 2002 (Box 138, Folder 10)
      - Ashburn, Delton A., granted 8 July 2002 (Box 138, Folder 11)
      - Atkins, Edward N., Jr., granted 10 October 2002 (Box 138, Folder 12)
      - Atkins, William Todd, granted 15 December 2002 (Box 138, Folder 13)
      - Atkinson, Elizabeth Moorefield, granted 11 January 2003 (Box 138, Folder 13a)
      - Banner, Ronnie Wood, granted 18 December 2002 (Box 138, Folder 14)
      - Barker, Michael Wayne, granted 15 December 2002 (Box 138, Folder 15)
      - Barricks, Donald Eugene, granted 15 December 2002 (Box 138, Folder 16)
      - Bass, Christopher Dwayne, granted 14 December 2002 (Box 138, Folder 17)
      - Battaglia, David Randolph, granted 4 December 2002 (Box 138, Folder 18)
      - Benmohamed, Manhal H., granted 14 December 2002 (Box 138, Folder 19)
      - Bishop, Fannie Holland, granted 9 July 2002 (Box 138, Folder 20)
      - Black, Mark K., granted 10 December 2002 (Box 139, Folder 1)
      - Blair, Donita Sue, granted 4 December 2002 (Box 139, Folder 2)
      - Bland, Myles Curtis Perrin, granted 11 January 2003 (Box 139, Folder 3)
      - Blevins, Jeffrey Scott, granted 9 October 2002 (Box 139, Folder 4)
      - Bone, Gary Donald, granted 6 September 2002 (Box 139, Folder 5)
      - Bostic, Betty Joeann, granted 22 January 2003 (Box 139, Folder 6)
      - Bowling, Frances Arlene, granted 9 January 2003 (Box 139, Folder 7)
      - Boyd, Sol Willie, granted 8 July 2002 (Box 139, Folder 8)
      - Bradley, Amos Calvin, granted 6 September 2002 (Box 139, Folder 9)
      - Brookman, Joseph W., Jr., granted 22 January 2003 (Box 139, Folder 10)
      - Brooks, Murphy Carrington, granted 22 January 2003 (Box 139, Folder 11)
      - Brooks, Virginia Anita, granted 22 January 2003 (Box 139, Folder 12)
      - Brown, Angelia Anita, granted 9 October 2002 (Box 139, Folder 13)
      - Brown, Monroe C., granted 10 October 2002 (Box 139, Folder 14)
      - Brownley, Lynn Curtis, granted 22 January 2003 (Box 139, Folder 15)
      - Buono, Bradley Paul, granted 10 July 2002 (Box 139, Folder 16)
      - Burns, Kevin Brian, granted 22 January 2003 (Box 139, Folder 17)
      - Burns, Phillip Ray, granted 22 January 2003 (Box 139, Folder 18)
      - Burton, Walter S., II, granted 12 June 2002 (Box 140, Folder 1)
      - Butterworth, Robert Wayne, granted 22 January 2003 (Box 140, Folder 2)
      - Cadd, James Robert, granted 22 January 2003 (Box 140, Folder 3)
      - Caizzo, Kevin A., granted 21 November 2002 (Box 140, Folder 4)
      - Calvaruso, Madeline, granted 22 January 2003 (Box 140, Folder 5)
      - Campbell, Margaret Ann, granted 22 January 2003 (Box 140, Folder 6)
      - Cantrell, Rocky C., granted 3 July 2002 (Box 140, Folder 7)
      - Canupp, Arthur Joseph, granted 21 November 2002 (Box 140, Folder 8)
      - Carroll, Winston Coolidge, granted 9 October 2002 (Box 140, Folder 9)
      - Carter, Maxine W., granted 22 January 2003 (Box 140, Folder 10)
      - Casey, Denise Loraine Hairston, granted 22 January 2003 (Box 140, Folder 11)
      - Castle, Charles S., granted 22 January 2003 (Box 140, Folder 12)
      - Chamblee, Darrell Dwayne, granted 11 January 2003 (Box 140, Folder 13)
      - Chitwood, Michael Wayne, granted 14 December 2002 (Box 140, Folder 14)
      - Clanton, Candyce Lee, granted 11 January 2003 (Box 140, Folder 15)
      - Cody, Donald Jerry, granted 9 January 2003 (Box 140, Folder 16)
      - Coe, Esther, granted 10 July 2002 (Box 140, Folder 17)
      - Coleman, Beacher Ralph, granted 22 January 2003 (Box 140, Folder 18)
      - Coleman, Harold Rickard, granted 22 January 2003 (Box 140, Folder 19)
      - Collins, Daniel Ted, granted 10 July 2002 (Box 140, Folder 20)
      - Compton, Ronald Wayne, granted 22 January 2003 (Box 141, Folder 1)
      - Connors, Kenneth Wayne, granted 11 January 2003 (Box 141, Folder 2)
      - Cook, Howard, Jr., granted 9 December 2002 (Box 141, Folder 3)
      - Corbin, Gregory A., granted 6 September 2002 (Box 141, Folder 4)
      - Corbin, Kevin Jay, granted 15 December 2002 (Box 141, Folder 5)
      - Cothron, Thomas Allen, granted 15 December 2002 (Box 141, Folder 6)
      - Cox, Billy Gene, granted 15 December 2002 (Box 141, Folder 7)
      - Crews, Rodney Lee, granted 22 January 2003 (Box 141, Folder 8)
      - Cronk, Timothy S., granted 5 August 2002 (Box 141, Folder 9)
      - Crum, Joe Junior, II, granted 6 November 2002 (Box 141, Folder 10)
      - Cubbage, Freeman Junior, granted 10 July 2002 (Box 141, Folder 11)
      - Cuffey, Sonnie G., granted 6 September 2002 (Box 141, Folder 12)
      - Culbertson, Johnnie E., granted 11 January 2003 (Box 141, Folder 13)
      - Curtis, Joseph Richard, granted 15 December 2002 (Box 142, Folder 1)
      - Daughtry, Nathaniel, granted 15 December 2002 (Box 142, Folder 2)
      - Davies, Doreen M., granted 6 September 2002 (Box 142, Folder 3)
      - Davis, Barry Liston, granted 15 December 2002 (Box 142, Folder 4)
      - Davis, Thurman Daniel, granted 15 December 2002 (Box 142, Folder 5)
      - DeBord, John Charles, granted 22 January 2003 (Box 142, Folder 6)
      - DeLoatch, Regena C., granted 9 January 2003 (Box 142, Folder 7)
      - Dodson, Loretha Darnell, granted 9 January 2003 (Box 142, Folder 8)
      - Dooley, Thomas Wayne, granted 22 January 2003 (Box 142, Folder 9)
      - Durrett, Tammy Jean Edwards, granted 14 December 2002 (Box 142, Folder 10)
      - Eaton, James Eugene, granted 11 January 2003 (Box 142, Folder 11)
      - Edwards, Arthur Lankford, granted 10 July 2002 (Box 142, Folder 12)
      - Ehle, Mary Ellen, granted 22 January 2003 (Box 142, Folder 13)
      - Ellerbe, Debra Michelle, granted 11 January 2003 (Box 142, Folder 14)
      - Evans, Martha Ann, granted 10 October 2002 (Box 142, Folder 15)
      - Faulkner, Raymond, granted 10 July 2002 (Box 142, Folder 16)
      - Feeny, Garland Mack, Sr., granted 22 January 2003 (Box 142, Folder 17)
      - Ferguson, Andrew Peter, granted 10 October 2002 (Box 142, Folder 18)
      - Finley, David Allen, granted 22 January 2003 (Box 142, Folder 19)
      - Fleck, Kevin James, granted 5 August 2002 (Box 142, Folder 20)
      - Floyd, Wendy, granted 22 January 2003 (Box 143, Folder 1)
      - Fortt, Veronica Lee, granted 15 December 2002 (Box 143, Folder 2)
      - Fox, Robert Lee, Sr., granted 15 December 2002 (Box 143, Folder 3)
      - Fragala, Michael A., granted 2 August 2002 (Box 143, Folder 4)
      - Funk, Albert Glynn, granted 11 January 2003 (Box 143, Folder 5)
      - Funk, Michael Joe, granted 14 December 2002 (Box 143, Folder 6)
      - Gamarra, Orlando A., granted 6 September 2002 (Box 143, Folder 7)
      - Garton, Fred Edward, granted 9 October 2002 (Box 143, Folder 8)
      - Gatewood, Roger Gregory, granted 6 September 2002 (Box 143, Folder 9)
      - Gibson, Cecil Wayne, granted 9 July 2002 (Box 143, Folder 10)
      - Glass, Michael Ellis, granted 11 January 2003 (Box 143, Folder 11)
      - Glover, Charles Edward, granted 11 January 2003 (Box 143, Folder 12)
      - Gody, Donald J., granted 9 January 2003 (Box 143, Folder 13)
      - Golden, Gary Weaver, granted 15 December 2002 (Box 143, Folder 14)
      - Good, Eddie Randall, granted 8 August 2002 (Box 143, Folder 15)
      - Goodrich, Richard George, granted 22 January 2003 (Box 143, Folder 16)
      - Graham, Dwight Brent, granted 22 January 2003 (Box 143, Folder 17)
      - Grant, Thomas Clifton, Jr., granted 14 December 2002 (Box 144, Folder 1)
      - Grimm, Timothy Lee, granted 22 January 2003 (Box 144, Folder 2)
      - Gross, Marion Marvin, III, granted 22 January 2003 (Box 144, Folder 3)
      - Groves, George Edward, granted 9 October 2002 (Box 144, Folder 4)
      - Gusler, David Clay, granted 9 October 2002 (Box 144, Folder 5)
      - Hall, Shirley Mae, granted 9 October 2002 (Box 144, Folder 6)
      - Hamrick, Shawn Alan, granted 13 June 2002 (Box 144, Folder 7)
      - Hathaway, Marcia Faye, granted 11 January 2003 (Box 144, Folder 8)
      - Harper, Linda Carol Yates, granted 22 January 2003 (Box 144, Folder 9)
      - Hart, Carlton Randolph, Jr., granted 10 October 2002 (Box 144, Folder 10)
      - Hartley, Janie Samantha, granted 11 January 2003 (Box 144, Folder 11)
      - Hartman, Johnnie Edward, granted 22 January 2003 (Box 144, Folder 12)
      - Harvey, Leon Griffin, granted 22 January 2003 (Box 144, Folder 13)
      - Hess, Michael Brent, granted 9 August 2002 (Box 144, Folder 14)
      - Hill, Sandra Leigh, granted 9 August 2002 (Box 144, Folder 15)
      - Holmes, Trina Nadine, granted 15 December 2002 (Box 144, Folder 16)
      - Holston, Calvin Morris, granted 14 December 2002 (Box 144, Folder 17)
      - Holt, Wilbur Dale, granted 22 January 2003 (Box 144, Folder 18)
      - Holzhauser, Kevin Dale, granted 6 September 2002 (Box 145, Folder 1)
      - Hopkins, Ronald Wayne, Sr., granted 9 October 2002 (Box 145, Folder 2)
      - Hua, Van Quoc, granted 14 December 2002 (Box 145, Folder 3)
      - Hudgins, Wise Warren, granted 14 December 2002 (Box 145, Folder 4)
      - Huffer, Paige Whetzel, granted 9 October 2002 (Box 145, Folder 5)
      - Jackson, Charlyne Marie, granted 6 August 2002 (Box 145, Folder 6)
      - Jackson, Karon Lynn, granted 9 July 2002 (Box 145, Folder 7)
      - James, Randall Scott, granted 22 January 2003 (Box 145, Folder 7a)
      - Jenkins, Clarence Leonard, granted 22 January 2003 (Box 145, Folder 8)
      - Jernigan, Joseph K., granted 22 January 2003 (Box 145, Folder 9)
      - Johns, Dewey Lee, granted 14 December 2002 (Box 145, Folder 10)
      - Johnson, Darryl Wayne, granted 6 September 2002 (Box 145, Folder 11)
      - Johnson, Stephen Lee, granted 22 January 2003 (Box 145, Folder 12)
      - Joyce, Arthur Bert, granted 22 January 2003 (Box 145, Folder 13)
      - Kassir, Nabil D., granted 22 January 2003 (Box 145, Folder 14)
      - Kebede, Yalemberhan, granted 22 January 2003 (Box 146, Folder 1)
      - Keeter, Phillip Lee, granted 22 January 2003 (Box 146, Folder 2)
      - Kerr, Dennis Rosser, granted 14 December 2002 (Box 146, Folder 3)
      - Kibler, Nancy Leigh, granted 22 January 2003 (Box 146, Folder 4)
      - Kinney, Kandi, granted 9 July 2002 (Box 146, Folder 5)
      - Konstantinakos, Sotirios, granted 2 August 2002 (Box 146, Folder 6)
      - Lacey, John David, granted 9 July 2002 (Box 146, Folder 7)
      - Lang, Nicole E., granted 14 December 2002 (Box 146, Folder 8)
      - Lankford, Stephen Troy, granted 15 December 2002 (Box 146, Folder 9)
      - Lawson, Karlous Keith, granted 12 June 2002 (Box 146, Folder 10)
      - Layne, Chad C., granted 15 December 2002 (Box 146, Folder 11)
      - Lee, Ruth Odessa Bell, granted 14 December 2002 (Box 146, Folder 12)
      - Litten, Christopher Lynn, granted 22 January 2003 (Box 146, Folder 13)
      - Liverman, Vasatie, granted 9 August 2002 (Box 146, Folder 14)
      - Long, Cornelius Norvell, granted 15 December 2002 (Box 146, Folder 15)
      - Louk, Laura Erwin Lacey, granted 22 January 2003 (Box 146, Folder 16)
      - Luter, Michael Andrew, granted 10 October 2002 (Box 146, Folder 17)
      - Lux, Herbert W., Jr., granted 15 December 2002 (Box 146, Folder 18)
      - Lyautey, Kathleen Ann, granted 8 July 2002 (Box 146, Folder 19)
      - Lyautey, Terry Lee Edward, granted 8 July 2002 (Box 146, Folder 20)
      - Martin, Alfonza, granted 22 January 2003 (Box 147, Folder 1)
      - Martin, James Michael, granted 21 November 2002 (Box 147, Folder 2)
      - Martin, Johnny Ray, granted 9 July 2002 (Box 147, Folder 3)
      - Massenburg, Herbert T., granted 22 January 2003 (Box 147, Folder 4)
      - McClain, Sean Ian, granted 10 July 2002 (Box 147, Folder 5)
      - McCune, Sidney Marshall, Jr., granted 10 July 2002 (Box 147, Folder 6)
      - McGee, James Elliott, granted 22 January 2003 (Box 147, Folder 7)
      - McSwain, Robert De-L-Carlo, granted 11 January 2003 (Box 147, Folder 8)
      - Meadows, James Lorn, granted 10 July 2002 (Box 147, Folder 9)
      - Metichecchia, Thomas, granted 2 August 2002 (Box 147, Folder 10)
      - Michael, Stephen Lee, granted 14 December 2002 (Box 147, Folder 11)
      - Milde, Paul Vincent, III, granted 5 September 2002 (Box 147, Folder 12)
      - Monroe, Savola Ray, granted 15 December 2002 (Box 147, Folder 13)
      - Morgan, Irene J., granted 15 December 2002 (Box 147, Folder 14)
      - Mosby, Theresa Gale, granted 21 November 2002 (Box 147, Folder 15)
      - Moses, Todd Vincent, granted 11 January 2003 (Box 147, Folder 16)
      - Mullins, Gary Clell, granted 10 October 2002 (Box 147, Folder 17)
      - Mullins, Johnny C., Jr., granted 14 December 2002 (Box 147, Folder 18)
      - Myers, Kelly Ferrell, granted 14 December 2002 (Box 147, Folder 19)
      - Nash, Michael Anthony, granted 21 November 2002 (Box 148, Folder 1)
      - Nery, Robert, III, granted 6 August 2002 (Box 148, Folder 2)
      - Newberger, Matthew William, granted 10 July 2002 (Box 148, Folder 3)
      - Nixon, John Henry, granted 14 December 2002 (Box 148, Folder 4)
      - Orino, William Harold, granted 14 December 2002 (Box 148, Folder 5)
      - Pafford, Amos Kent, granted 24 August 2002 (Box 148, Folder 6)
      - Paige, Tina Michelle, granted 14 December 2002 (Box 148, Folder 7)
      - Pankey, Martha Trent, granted 7 October 2002 (Box 148, Folder 8)
      - Pare, Jacques W., granted 22 January 2003 (Box 148, Folder 9)
      - Patterson, Paul Leroy, granted 22 January 2003 (Box 148, Folder 10)
      - Payne, Robert Steven, granted 24 August 2002 (Box 148, Folder 11)
      - Pearson, Percy L., granted 6 September 2002 (Box 148, Folder 12)
      - Perkins, Colleen Peterman, granted 10 October 2002 (Box 148, Folder 13)
      - Peters, Connie Suzanne, granted 14 December 2002 (Box 148, Folder 14)
      - Petty, Robin LaTanyia, granted 12 June 2002 (Box 148, Folder 15)
      - Pierce, Cherie Inez, granted 10 October 2002 (Box 148, Folder 16)
      - Phillips, Vanessa Cox, granted 6 November 2002 (Box 148, Folder 17)
      - Porter, Willie W., granted 14 December 2002 (Box 148, Folder 18)
      - Powell, Roberta Marie, granted 13 June 2002 (Box 149, Folder 1)
      - Price, Edward Franklin, granted 9 October 2002 (Box 149, Folder 2)
      - Price, Linda I., granted 10 July 2002 (Box 149, Folder 3)
      - Price, Robert Arthur, granted 14 December 2002 (Box 149, Folder 4)
      - Quesenberry, Robert Maurice, granted 10 July 2002 (Box 149, Folder 5)
      - Ragland, Carl Westley, granted 14 December 2002 (Box 149, Folder 6)
      - Ramsey, Joseph Barry, granted 22 January 2003 (Box 149, Folder 7)
      - Ramsey, Larry Melvin, granted 9 October 2002 (Box 149, Folder 8)
      - Ratliff, Arvil Ray, granted 10 October 2002 (Box 149, Folder 9)
      - Reedy, Jacob Edward, granted 14 December 2002 (Box 149, Folder 10)
      - Reynolds, John C., granted 15 December 2002 (Box 149, Folder 11)
      - Riffee, Robert Wright, granted 22 January 2003 (Box 149, Folder 12)
      - Robinson, James Gary, granted 8 August 2002 (Box 149, Folder 13)
      - Robinson, Katherine Anne Hunnicutt, granted 9 August 2002 (Box 149, Folder 14)
      - Rodgers, Krindolph, Jr., granted 21 November 2002 (Box 149, Folder 15)
      - Rosamond, Brenda Denise, granted 14 December 2002 (Box 149, Folder 16)
      - Rowland, Steve Allen, granted 8 August 2002 (Box 149, Folder 17)
      - Ruffin, Ralph Eugene, granted 11 January 2003 (Box 149, Folder 18)
      - Saleem, Humera Mariam, granted 15 December 2002 (Box 150, Folder 1)
      - Sanders, Jimmy, granted 9 August 2002 (Box 150, Folder 2)
      - Sanders, Michael William, granted 24 August 2002 (Box 150, Folder 3)
      - Saunders, William Otho, Jr., granted 22 January 2003 (Box 150, Folder 4)
      - Savage, Kim Celeste, granted 15 December 2002 (Box 150, Folder 5)
      - Scrodin, Douglas John, granted 11 January 2003 (Box 150, Folder 6)
      - Scrogham, Weldon Wright, granted 15 December 2002 (Box 150, Folder 7)
      - Seay, William E., Jr., granted 12 June 2002 (Box 150, Folder 8)
      - Shaikh, Asif, granted 9 January 2003 (Box 150, Folder 9)
      - Shepard, Barry Calvesta, granted 31 July 2002 (Box 150, Folder 10)
      - Shinaberry, Michele Lee, granted 9 January 2003 (Box 150, Folder 11)
      - Sink, Earl Matthew, granted 9 January 2003 (Box 150, Folder 12)
      - Small, Dennis N., granted 11 June 2002 (Box 150, Folder 13)
      - Smith, Elsie O, granted 10 October 2002 (Box 150, Folder 14)
      - Smith, Glenn W., granted 24 August 2002 (Box 150, Folder 15)
      - Smith, Jason Stover, granted 10 October 2002 (Box 150, Folder 16)
      - Smith, Phebean M., granted 12 June 2002 (Box 150, Folder 17)
      - Smith, Russell Allen, granted 22 January 2003 (Box 150, Folder 18)
      - Smith, Shirley Ann Bassette, granted 9 August 2002 (Box 150, Folder 19)
      - Snyder, Angela Anna-Marie, granted 11 January 2003 (Box 151, Folder 1)
      - Spang, Jeffrey John, granted 24 August 2002 (Box 151, Folder 2)
      - Spraker, Erron Philip, granted 6 September 2002 (Box 151, Folder 3)
      - Stilwell, Manuel Thomas, Jr., granted 6 August 2002 (Box 151, Folder 4)
      - Strange, Jimmy Ray, granted 22 January 2003 (Box 151, Folder 5)
      - Stump, Debra L., granted 11 January 2003 (Box 151, Folder 6)
      - Sullivan, Bert Ralph, granted 22 January 2003 (Box 151, Folder 7)
      - Swingler-Page, Ruth Ann, granted 9 July 2002 (Box 151, Folder 8)
      - Taylor, Gertrude H., granted 6 September 2002 (Box 151, Folder 9)
      - Taylor, William, granted 15 April 2002 (Box 151, Folder 10)
      - Tchaika, Boris, granted 6 August 2002 (Box 151, Folder 11)
      - Thompson, Jack Russell, granted 9 January 2003 (Box 151, Folder 12)
      - Trumbull, Lyanne, granted 9 July 2002 (Box 151, Folder 13)
      - Trusty, Milton Grant, granted 15 December 2002 (Box 151, Folder 14)
      - Tsimbidis, Nikolaos S., granted 12 June 2002 (Box 151, Folder 15)
      - Turner, Nancy Arlene, granted 9 July 2002 (Box 151, Folder 16)
      - Turner, Sheila Denise, granted 9 January 2003 (Box 151, Folder 17)
      - Tyler, Roy A., granted 18 November 2002 (Box 151, Folder 18)
      - Umberger, Jimmy Gene Autry, granted 15 December 2002 (Box 151, Folder 19)
      - VanMeter, Horace Clinton, granted 11 January 2003 (Box 151, Folder 20)
      - Walker, Carolyn Faye, granted 24 August 2002 (Box 152, Folder 1)
      - Waller, Alvins Dennis, granted 10 October 2002 (Box 152, Folder 2)
      - Warner, Perry S., granted 24 August 2002 (Box 152, Folder 3)
      - Warren, Van Vincent, granted 10 October 2002 (Box 152, Folder 4)
      - Washington, Kenneth L., granted 13 June 2002 (Box 152, Folder 5)
      - Watt, James, Jr., granted 21 November 2002 (Box 152, Folder 6)
      - Weeks, William H., granted 4 December 2002 (Box 152, Folder 7)
      - Whitaker, Phillip Ray, granted 11 January 2003 (Box 152, Folder 8)
      - Wilkerson, Gary F., granted 24 August 2002 (Box 152, Folder 9)
      - Wilkins, Barbara A., granted 15 December 2002 (Box 152, Folder 10)
      - Williams, Bobby Edwards, granted 7 August 2002 (Box 152, Folder 11)
      - Williams, Glenn Lewis, granted 6 September 2002 (Box 152, Folder 12)
      - Willis, Jeffrey Franklin, granted 9 July 2002 (Box 152, Folder 13)
      - Wilson, Clifton William, granted 15 December 2002 (Box 152, Folder 14)
      - Wilson, Stanley E., granted 14 December 2002 (Box 152, Folder 15)
      - Wilson, Thomas Edwin, granted 22 January 2003 (Box 152, Folder 16)
      - Wingfield, Aubrey Hatcher, granted 7 October 2002 (Box 152, Folder 17)
      - Wolf, John Edward, Jr., granted 17 May 2002 (Box 152, Folder 18)
      - Wroten, Sharon Kay, granted 9 July 2002 (Box 153, Folder 1)
      - Wyatt, Angela Michelle, granted 24 August 2002 (Box 153, Folder 2)
      - Yates, Ricky Allen, granted 8 August 2002 (Box 153, Folder 3)
      - Young, Troy Richard, Sr., granted 15 December 2002 (Box 153, Folder 4)
      - Yount, Tamara Nicklow, granted 22 January 2003 (Box 153, Folder 5)
      - Yuille, Lucinda Patrick, granted 24 August 2002 (Box 153, Folder 6)
    - 23 January 2003 to 14 January 2004 (Accession 42418)
      - Abrams, Gloria P., granted 31 December 2003 (Box 154, Folder 1)
      - Ackerman, Kevin Joseph, granted 16 June 2003 (Box 154, Folder 2)